What are you doing?
Did I tell you?
Don't mess around with my desk.
I bought milk and snacks.
He said that this shop is very delicious.
Try eating first?
I'm sorry.
Did you see that?
That my work is broken
Like this, who will be responsible?
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to.
Sorry?
Sorry, will beauty come back?
Why are you so busy with my life?
You know that?
That I'm bored.
I'm annoyed
And most importantly
I don't want to see your face.
I thought we'd be good neighbors.
I saw you tired.
Work hard
I just want you to eat something delicious.
Plant elder
I was very wrong, right?
I'm your problem, right?
Then keep going.
I won't let you see your face again.
Hello, I would like to be a latte ice milk.
Which size is better to accept? Erm.
Take it as a grand day
Eh?
Can I have it?
Add two thousand vinns.
Wait a minute
Thank you.
I'm done.
I'm happy.
Thank you very much
Bye bye
Good bye.
Elder, Master Nititi, he looks strange, strange, strange.
T
Are you angry with me?
No.
If not angry, then come to eat boiled rice together first.
I got up early in the morning, intended to make porridge for me.
No.
I don't like boiled rice.
This one is black.
Hiding the trend with a cough of power.
If you guys stare at this picture, it looks good.
She'll see the insert inside.
Ouch, applause. Students applaud.
We talk to the stars, our children talk to the stars.
Bye-bye today.
Teen Teen, what's wrong with you today?
Uh, what did you say, June?
Just now, Ejun asked if you were okay, walking all day.
Odd is nothing. Then we'll go to the bathroom first. I'll follow you.
I think there must be something for sure. It just doesn't tell us.
Sun, hello.
You've been looking for us for a long time here.
Why didn't you call me?
Do like you have our number.
Uh, let me have our number.
But do you have anything with me?
Oh, I came through this building, so I bought some snacks.
Thank you very much
I bought a lot.
I can't eat all alone.
Then I would like to share friends.
Yes, sir.
Why not?
And if you don't hurry anywhere, come and eat together first
Ouch, this person is good.
I'm not
Ouch, pretend that this person I sure
So touchy?
You people must be mine.
I will take this person. Don't mess around.
Take it now. A million hearts.
Good. Very good.
Very good, Mom.
Hey you
Go for a moment and get a lot of food.
I carry my favorite Thai dessert. You really deserve my best friend.
Let me eat some
Don't come to compete with me
I can't eat
Gumini.
Much more delicious
Do you eat?
Is the dessert delicious? Everyone
Very delicious, but I don't share it with you. If you want to eat, go to eat by yourself.
Friends, friends.
What are you eating? Don't be too much.
Well, I will tell you that these snacks, Sun, he bought them for me to eat.
I don't eat
Who will eat?
I eat myself
Is this evening free?
Oh, free.
Then let's go eat. Nanny.
Yes.
Ugh!
Oh, rich.
And we go together?
Go. Free stuff. I like it.
We probably only went to two people because another friend, he wouldn't dare to go.
E June
I went to eat with you too.
Hello, Mom.
Yes, sir.
Eat fully. I'll have a meal. Nanny. As for yourself, don't worry. Line told the botanical to be comfortable.
Botanical elder
Phi Phra
Are you angry with me?
That I invited and never will be free
Going home late, never thought to call
Yeah, yeah.
I am an outsider
I saw Sun. He called you, didn't he?
Then why do I have to call you again?
It's not the same.
And how is it not the same?
So if I make you uncomfortable, I'm sorry.
Yeah, forget it.
Study
Please.
No.
So take this.
Are you missing me?
No.
I'm not touchy.
Elder
Oh, haven't seen each other for a long time. Clear sky. Aunt Tae came back from abroad?
Yes, I came back for a week. Just come to do business around here.
Oh, this is my brother.
Nice to meet you.
But I haven't seen each other for a long time. Leave a pile of fresh strings.
Use the same pattern again?
Yes, use the same pattern
Okay, the next day, go to eat together. I host myself.
Okay, elder. See you later. Fah Clear, please go first.
Yes.
Long time no see
More beautiful than a pile
Keep it empty.
To feed for a while
Do we know that when you're uncomfortable, you like to sit here?
And do we like it?
I like it. I like it.
But do you know?
The first day I met you
You made me late.
Also made me scold the teacher anymore, I will call you a nemesis
To say that, we are also cute. Earth
What do you say?
We are also cute. Earth
Don't tell me.
You secretly like me.
Do you eat snacks?
Hey.
No.
Indulge
Do you eat this snack? I like it.
No.
What are you guys doing today?
Nothing.
I’m going to the bathroom first.
I’m going to buy water first.
There must be something in these two.
What are you doing?
Normally, I see you more cheerful.
There is nothing uncomfortable to tell me.
Anyway, I and you are friends.
To vent something
I think it's better to keep it alone.
Well, I have a little problem with Phi Phra.
Well, I spilled water on his work, but I don't think he's so angry. Even my face, he doesn't want to look at it yet.
Yeah.
Then take like this. During this time, you come to sleep in my room first. You better go home to elder Tak.
Um, it's good. In case of anything, it will improve, but I would like to go home to collect things first.
Um, but I will go out to do business as well. You will finish packing and call.
Yeah, see you later.
Call, never answer, never free. What are you doing? Other people answer the call. Very good. What are you looking at like this?
How long have you arrived?
It's been a while.
Uh, this is the shirt you forgot.
Earth.
Yes.
I want to tell Earth that
About last night we
What is it
Forget it.
It's just normal for people to have something.
Well, I don't know when it happened, when it happened.
And how is it like this?
I just wanted to tell Earth that
I will say
Are you drunk?
The whole happened last night.
It's because you're drunk.
I didn't want it to happen.
It was just our mistake, right?
It's not like that, Earth. I just want to explain what happened.
Forget it.
Forget to forget it.
But you don't have to be scared.
That I will mess with you again
Next, I will not show you my face again.
Elder, I would like to go to sleep in my friend's room for a few days.
No, why didn't I go?
It's very uncomfortable with me, isn't it?
Yeah, yeah.
Stay with me
It wouldn't be as happy as it was with Sun.
Seen with it
Make a little smile, big smile
Probably very happy, right?
Really ask
Who said that going to sleep in a friend's room
Going to sleep like it, right?
Huh?
Answer
Why?
Or who am I going to have with?
Why are you interested?
I really asked
Have you ever cared about my feelings?
Have you ever cared about me?
I am your annoyance.
Even my face.
You still don't want to look.
I wouldn't be in your eyes.
Elder November
Botak
Oh.
Are you awake?
Come here.
Sit here.
Come sit here.
And are you not eating?
No, I eat full all night and
Very good mouth
Will hit
Or not good.
You eat a little bit. Eat a lot. Delicious?
Yes, sir.